Finding aid for the Robert A. Kennard Papers LSC.2351
UCLA Library Special Collections
Robert A. Kennard papers
1953-2015
UCLA Library Special Collections
Kennard, Gail
Kennard, Robert A.
LSC.2351
25.2 Linear Feet (58 boxes, 1 half box, 5 shoeboxes, and 2 flat boxes)
250 Linear Feet (125 unprocessed architectural rolls)
Robert A. Kennard (1920-1995) was an African American architect in Los Angeles. He designed over 40 residences and later focused on public works, including Carson City Hall and Community Center and the Los Angeles Police Department (LAPD) Headquarters. The collection contains administrative records about his firm, Kennard Design Group (KDG); site plans, planning reports, and studies; photographs, negatives, and slides of completed projects; and documentation about Kennard's work in the National Organization of Minority Architects (NOMA) and mentorship to architects of color.
Conditions Governing Access
Portions of collection unprocessed. Material in the Architectural Plans series is unavailable for access. Please see LSC's Access to Unprocessed Collections Policy for more information about levels of discovery and access of special collections materials and registering interest in unprocessed collections.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIO MATERIALS: Audio materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email spec-coll@library.ucla.edu.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Gail Kennard, 2017.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9992418293606533
Biography/History
Robert A. Kennard was born in Los Angeles, CA in 1920. He served as a lieutenant in the Army in World War II and the Korean War, attended Pasadena City College, and earned an architectural degree at USC. In 1957 he established his own firm, later known as Kennard Design Group, the oldest African American architecture firm in Los Angeles. The firm designed more than 700 projects in Southern California, beginning with over 40 residences completed through the early 1960s. One of his first homes, the Zeiger Residence in Laurel Canyon has been designated as a City of Los Angeles Cultural-Historic Monument. In the mid-1960s he shifted his practice to public work. Notable projects include the City of Carson City Hall and Community Center, designed with architects Robert Alexander and Frank Sata, Van Nuys State Office Building with architect Harold Williams, and Parking Structures 1, 3 and 4 at the Los Angeles International Airport. Two of his last projects completed in the mid-1990s were the City of Los Angeles 77th Street Police Headquarters in which the community room is named in his honor, and a new entrance to the Hollywood Bowl.
Kennard Design Group garnered awards from the American Institute of Architects (AIA) and California Preservation Foundation for its work as associate architect in the redesign and expansion of Los Angeles' Central Library. Kennard encouraged other minority and women architects to enter the profession, and he was active in the both the Los Angeles and California chapters of the American Institute of Architects (AIA) and in numerous community organizations including the Inner City Cultural Center where he served as president of the board with the late actor, Gregory Peck. He was recognized as a fellow of the AIA, a Distinguished Alumnus of the USC School of Architecture, and he received the Whitney M. Young Jr. Citation from the AIA in 1991 for his contributions to the profession. He died in Los Angeles, CA, in March 1995.
Source: Myrna Oliver, "R. A. Kennard; Prominent Black Architect," Los Angeles Times, March 29, 1995, http://articles.latimes.com/1995-03-29/news/mn-48295_1_los-angeles.
Scope and Content
The collection contains administrative records about Robert Kennard's architecture firm, Kennard Design Group (KDG); site plans, planning reports, and studies; and documentation about Kennard's work in the National Organization of Minority Architects (NOMA) and mentorship to architects of color. The bulk of the material consists of photographs and negatives of KDG architectural projects, in addition to color slides and microfilm of drawings. Also contained within the collection are 125 rolled architectural drawings for KDG projects and 7 boxes of plans for Kennard's personal residence. The collection also contains a student portfolio of Kennard's.
Arrangement
This collection has been arranged in the following series:
Series 1: Kennard Design Group administrative records, 1953-2000s
Subseries 1.1: General administrative records, 1953-2000s
Subseries 1.2: Awards, 1974-2000
Subseries 1.3: Press and marketing, 1980-1999
Subseries 1.4: Correspondence, 1954-1995
Series 2: Kennard Design Group projects, 1957-2015
Subseries 2.1: Los Angeles County, 1957-2003
Subseries 2.2: Non-Los Angeles County Southern California, 1970-1988
Subseries 2.3: Northern California, 1968-2015
Subseries 2.4: Other US locations, 1970s-1980s
Subseries 2.5: International, 1970s-1983
Subseries 2.6: Color slides, microfilm, and negatives, 1960s-1995
Series 3: Architectural plans and drawings, 1959-1995
Series 4: Increasing diversity in architecture, 1976-1994
Related Materials
Interview of Robert Kennard [oral history transcript] / Wesley H. Henderson, interviewer. UCLA Library Special Collections, Center for Oral History Research interview, 1990-1991. Available at UCLA Library Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library, UCLA.
Golden State Mutual Life Insurance Company records (Collection 1434). Available at UCLA Library Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library, UCLA.
Other Finding Aids
A digital copy of the project inventory is available via this link: Link to KDG project inventory
African American architects -- California -- Los Angeles; Kennard, Gail; Kennard, Robert A. -- Archives; Kennard Design Group (KDG Architecture and Planning)
- Series 1: Kennard Design Group administrative records, 1953-2000s
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIO MATERIALS: Audio materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email spec-coll@library.ucla.edu.
  Scope and Contents
  This series comprises administrative documents, awards, marketing documents, reports, legal and financial information, newspaper articles, and personal correspondence realted to the operations of KDG.
  - Subseries 1.1: General administrative records, 1953-2000s
    This subseries includes such items as professional photographs, listings of Board members for organizations that Kennard was a part of, examples of brochures, but also more critical administrative documents that contribute to an understanding of how Kennard ran his business, including documents outlining the dissolution of an earlier iteration of the KDG company.
    - St. John's Legal, 1970-1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - St. John's Lutheran Church, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Synanon - Legal, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Legal Folder - Third College, 1970-1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Kennard and Silvers / Pollak Barsocchini Associates (KS/PBA) Legal File, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - More Oakland Residential Housing (MORH) Legal, 1970-1979 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
    - Simon Miller Legal, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Ronald W. Martin Legal, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - St. John's Lutheran Church Legal, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Wyle Laboratories Legal, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Hunter's Point Site 1 - Litigation, 1970-1979 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Crenshaw Legal File, 1970-1979 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Roosevelt Jr. High Legal, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (WMATA) Legal, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Legal File, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Kennard Delahouise and Gault (Architecture and Planning)/ Gault-Plesset Corporation (KDG/GP) Sublease, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Sublease Info, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Kennard Delahouise and Gault (Architecture and Planning) (KDG) Office Bank and Costs (Wilshire-Highland), 1976 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - 7700 Edgewater Dr - Rent, 1974-1977 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Oakland - Lease, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Wilshire Highland Construction, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Burglary, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Manhattan Life - Inactive Policies, Correspondence, Invoices, 1970-1980 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Automobile Insurance, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Business Travel - AETNA Life Insurance Company (AETNA), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Worker's Compensation - Inactive Policies, Correspondence, Invoices, 1975-1979 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Umbrella Liability - Inactive policies, Correspondence, Invoices, 1977-1980 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Kennard Silvers (KS) Dissolution, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Kennard Delahouise and Gault (Architecture and Planning) (KDG) Corporate Movers - Robert A Kennard (RAK) - Jeffrey M. Gault (JMG), Buy/Sell Agreement, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - KDG Corporate Movers - RAK, RJD, JMG Buy/Sell Agreement, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - KDG Corporate - Delahousie Stock Sale, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - KDG Corporate Movers - RAK, RJD, JMG Partnership, 1974-1978 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - KDG Corporate Movers - Gualt Stock Sale/Downs Purchase, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - KDG Corporation - Delahousie Release or Stock Pledge, 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - KDG Corporate Movers - Kennard/Silvers Partnership, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Insurance Information, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - KDG Corporate Affairs - Arms Inc., 1970-1979 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - KDG Financial Statements, 1973-1977 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Financial Statements, 1970-1979 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Internal Revenue Service (IRS), 1975-1977 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Audit For 1975 (Conducted in 1978) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - KDG Financial Reports, 1982-1991 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - KDG Financial Reports, 1957-1981 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Kennard and Silver's AWA 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - KDG Partnership Return 1975, 1975-1978 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - KDG Partnership Return 1974 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Kennard and Silver's Partnership Return 1970, 1971, 1972, 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - KDG - Al Whittle Associates (AWA) returns 1974-1978 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Dissolution Agreement - Kennard and Silvers, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Partnership Agreements, 1966-1973 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Buy-Sell Agreements, 1980s (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Buy/Sell Agreements, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Publicity and News Re: The Firm, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Agency for International Development - Zimbabwe Mission, 1975-1982 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Zimbabwe Business Journals, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Zimbabwe Transportation - News Clippings, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Zimbabwe Housing/Planning- News Clippings, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Zimbabwe News Clippings - Hotel, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Zimbabwe - Zanu Headquarters, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Architecture and Firm Selection Comments, 1966-1969 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - KDG Newsline - Spring 1984 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Kennard Agenda, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Funeral Arrangements - Robert Kennard, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Personal Robert Kennard Documents, 1987-1999 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - KDG Folders with Information, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Business Development, 1989-1992 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Business Legislative Files, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - American Institute of Architects - Agenda - 1992 Meeting (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Architecture License - Virginia, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - National Council of Architectural Registration Board Certificate, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - California Architecture License, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Act to Regulate Practice of Architecture, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - California Renewal License, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia Architecture License Title 54, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Professional events, 1990s (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - State of California - Architecture License, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - District of Columbia Architecture License, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Board of Architecture Application, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Board of Architectural Examiners Documents, 1975-1982 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Acknowledgement of Receipt of Handicap, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Robert Kennard Reinstatement Charge, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Cultural Affairs Commission Documents, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - California Council, American Institute of Architects - Membership - Related Notes, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - LA - A/A - Forum '81, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - University of Southern California (USC) Dean's Advisory Board and Dean Collection, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Support to Transafrica, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Sigma Pi Phi Fraternity, 1984-1996 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Fraternity of the Music Center Support, 1978-1984 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Nomination for "Rebuild LA" Committee, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - KDG personal photographs, circa 1970s-2000s (Box 8, Folder 3-5)
    - Appointment Books, 1974-1993 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Inner City Cultural Center New Board Members, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - A History and Directory of the College of Fellows, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Central City Federal Biographies, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Robert Kennard Photographs (Professional), 1984-1992 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Kennard Design Group (KDG) Brochures and Letterhead, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Kennard Design Group (KDG) Personal, circa 1990s-2000s (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Kennard Design Group (KDG) Personal, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - "Toward a Quality City" Inglewood, CA: Community Review Program report, 1972 (Box 62)
    - "Grand Avenue" book, 1980 (Box 63)
    - Plan and Profile Drawings of Rail Transit Alternatives report, 1993 (Box 62)
    - Boxed slides, 1993-1996 (Box 60)
      This box contains color slides documenting the MTA transit-based housing symposium (Willow Street site); National Organization of Minority Architects (NOMA) tribute; UC Irvine; Robert Kennard Memorial Tribute.
    - Audiocassettes, undated (Box 60)
      This box contains 3 audiocassettes with the following labels: "Blue Martini," "Hadi Bedrakhan," "KDG Slide Presentation."
  - Subseries 1.2: Awards, 1974-2000
    This subseries contains awards and award submissions to a variety of different architectural competitions, in addition to exhibits in international or national architectural exhibitions.
    - U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD) Awards Feedback, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Kennard Design Group (KDG) Architectural Educational Certificate, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Architecture D'Aujourd HUI Exhibit, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - 7th Biennial HUD Award For Design Excellence Submission, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - American Institute of Architects (AIA) Council Publicity Clipping, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Robert Kennard Bio For Awards, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Robert Kennard Awards, 1989-1990s (Box 26, Folder 7-8)
    - AIA - LA '84 Olympic Architects, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Outstanding Engineering Merit Award, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - AIA Honor Award Submission, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 1.3: Press and marketing, 1980-1999
    This subseries consists primarily of newspaper and magazine clippings covering the 40th anniversary of KDG, Robert Kennard's death, and press coverage of various projects. Also included are clippings pertaining to Zimbabwe in the early 1980s, likely collected in relation to the Zanu (PF) Headquarters proposed project, and a small amount of marketing materials.
    - Marketing - 40th Anniversary, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Marketing - Life and Style, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Los Angeles Magazine - Like Father, Like Daughters, 1980-1989 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Roybal Institute for Gerontology Project: Marketing & Press Clippings, 1990s (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Hollywood Bowl - Press Clippings, 1990s (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - 77th Street Police Press Clippings, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 3-4)
    - Figueroa Court Apartment Projects (Marketing from Design Cost Data Magazine), 1999 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Valley Senior Housing Marketing - Grapevine, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - King/Drew Medical Center Projects (Clippings and Magazines), 1990-1999 (Box 11, Folder 6-7)
    - LA Central Library Press Clippings, 1990-1999 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - USC Scholarship - Press Clippings, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Fame Projects - Press Clippings, 1990-1999 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Film Transitions - Press Clippings, 1990-1999 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Robert Kennard Obituary - Heritage Magazine, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Robert Kennard Obituary - Update Magazine, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - USC Memorial Scholarship Mention of Robert Kennard, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Robert Kennard in Memoriam - LA Architect, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - In Memoriam - "Info-Mania" Publication, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Robert Kennard Death - Greater LA African-American Chamber of Commerce Newsletter, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Robert Kennard Death - Architect Newsletter, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Robert Kennard Death - Wave Newspapers, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Robert Kennard Death - Napolitano Communications or Construction Link, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Angeles Magazine - Article with Robert Kennard and Daughter, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - KDG - Newsline Newspapers, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Zimbabwe - Political/Social/Historical News Clippings, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Zimbabwe - Zanu HQs and Political, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Zimbabwe - Misc. News Clippings, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Zimbabwe - Architecture News Clippings, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Zimbabwe - Civil Engineers - Building/Construction News Clippings, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Zimbabwe - News Clippings - Economic Issues/Business, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Zimbabwe - News Clippings - Energy, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Zimbabwe - News Clippings - Health Clinics/Hospitals, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Subseries 1.4: Correspondence, 1954-1995
    This subseries contains correspondence from both individuals and organizations from and to Robert Kennard. Included is correspondence about Robert Kennard's passing and a note from Mayor Tom Bradley.
    - Zimbabwe Correspondence, 1982-1985 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Assorted Personal Correspondences, 1990s (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Robert Kennard Death - Personal Correspondences, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 3-4)
    - American Institute of Architects Correspondences, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Correspondences - References for Fellow Architects in their License, 1980s-1990s (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Correspondences Against Budget Items (Removal of Board of Architectural Examiners), 1979 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Joe Sam Correspondence, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Los Angeles Conservancy Membership, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - AIA Chapter Nominations, 1988-1992 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Consulting Engineers & Land Surveyors Minutes, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - California Council AIA - Minority & Women Business Enterprise Legislation Letter, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - AIA California Council Awards - Feedback, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Asbestos - Related Liability, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - National AIA Letter Re-South Africa Trip, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Senate Bill (SB) 1336 Letters, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Registered Architects Surveys (AIA), 1954-1969 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - American Institute of Architects Letters - Membership Related, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - AIA - Political Involvement, 1977-1980 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - AIA Bylaws/Ethical Principles, 1977-1980 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - National Architecture Accrediting Board (NAAB) nominations, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - California Office of Minority Business Enterprise, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - AIA Documents (Bylaws, Dues), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - AIA Letters, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Advisory Review Panel Correspondence, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence - Re: Robert Alexander Death - LA Architect, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - LA County Board of Supervisors, Architectural Eval Board - Seraphim Lamb Recommendations and Representation, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - UCLA Grad School of Arch & Urban Planning Splitting - Letter to GSAUP Board, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU) Donations - Foundation, 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - John W. Murray Commissioner, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence with Robert P. Madison and Representation, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Ebonics Support Group Correspondence and Events, 1985-1989 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Cal Poly Shadow Program Thanks, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Congratulations on the KDG Formation, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Series 2: Kennard Design Group projects, 1957-2015
  This series makes up the bulk of the collection and includes project documentation for work that KDG has completed over the years. Subseries 2.6 includes the photoslides that KDG had created for their projects.
  Arrangement
  Material has been arranged chronologically by project job. Projects are arranged into subseries geographically per the location of the project site.
  - Subseries 2.1: Los Angeles County, 1957-2003
    This subseries collects all of the projects that KDG completed and proposed in Los Angeles County, and includes site plans, photographs, transparencies, and negatives. KDG constructed many Los Angeles sites including the Los Angeles Police Department (LAPD) Headquarters, Carson City Hall and Community Center and many fire stations, churches, high schools, and university buildings across the county.
    - Tamarind Apartment (53), 1957 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Zeiger Residence (66), 1957 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Tung-Yen (T.Y.) Lin Engineering Site Plans and Pictures (72), 1958 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Eisler Ardmore Apartments (88), 1958 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Zeiger Residences (117), 1959 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Kennard's Residence - Hollywood Hills (126), 1960 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - First Unitarian Church (133), 1960 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Von Mel (152), 1961 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Eisler Ardmore Kingsley Apartment (163), 1961 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Culver City Unified School District (170), 1961 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Temple Akiba (188), 1962 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Hardyman Residence (205), 1963 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Congregation Emanuel (240), 1965 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Temple Solael (247), 1965 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Goodman Jewelers (251), 1965 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Lady Markell (252), 1965 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Hyde Park School (258), 1966 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Watts Happening Cultural Center (278), 1967 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Hyde Park Boulevard School (292), 1968 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - 102nd Street School (294), 1968 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Fire Station #33 (301), 1968 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Central City Community Mental Health Center (302), 1968 (Box 19, Folder 2-3, Box 62)
    - Bank of America Watts (305), 1969 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Lockheed, Engineering Research & Consulting (Inc.) (ERC) (309), 1969 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - St. Mark's Lutheran Church (316), 1969 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Hoover Elderly Housing Tumast Foundation (TUMAST) (317), 1969 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - St. John's Lutheran Church (324), 1969 (Box 20, Folder 3)